Danilo Isamu Inafuku

Software & Game Developer

+55 15 991849583

Sorocaba, São Paulo, Brasil

MisterProjectLC

https://misterprojectlc.github.io/

Resumo

I am a game developer interested in design, programming and writing. I have experience with engines such as Unity, Godot and Game Maker, and languages such as C#, Python, GDScript and C.

I've been interested in game development since I was 12, and have never looked back since. The magic of writing code and then seeing its logic materialize on-screen... It still affects me to this day. That is what I look for. To create, and to inspire.

Education

2019 - 2024

UFSCar Sorocaba

Bachelor in Computer Science

Experience

2022 – Currently

Lightmancer Studios - Bloodrush: Undying Wish

Director, Coordinator, Designer, Main Programmer, Writer

- Project management, scheduling meetings and planning deadlines.
- Design and implementation of combat mechanics, progression systems, UI and various visual effects.
- Game and narrative direction and overall vision.

2024

DOK Despachante

Junior PHP Developer

- Systems development with PHP, Laravel and Docker.
- · Feature creation and review.
- Codebase rework and restructuring.

2022 - 2024

SiDi - Samsung Projects in a 3D Environment

Intern

- Development with the Unity and Unreal engines.
- · Creation and review of new features.
- Work with a diverse team of programmers, designers and testers.

2020-202I

Ufscar Sorocaba - "Garibot" Project

Developer, Designer - Educational game

- Development and implementation of game mechanics and systems.
- Level design for several game stages.
- General game planning in relation to its educational mission.

2020 - 2024

Maritacas Gamedev - Game development club

Coordinator and Member

- Organization and planning of events and meetings.
- Supervision of ongoing projects.
- Design, development and creation of my own games.

Programming Languages

- C
- C++
- C#
- Python
- Java
- JavaScript
- PHP

Technologies

- Unity Engine
- Godot Engine

- Git
- HTML
- CSS
- SQL
- NodeJS
- Docker
- · DaVinci Resolve

Languages

- Brazilian Portuguese Native
- English Fluent
- German Intermediate

Projects

The full project list can be inspected through the link at the beginning of this document.

2022 – Currently

Bloodrush: Undying Wish

Top-down hack n' slash game with a dark fantasy aesthetic. Developed with the Godot Engine.

2022

Discord Bot - Galactic RPG

Bot for the Discord communication app, created to manage a small online RPG. Employs a Database to store players, weapons, commands and other game data. Developed using JavaScript and SQL.

202I

Kinetic

Fast-paced low-poly movement shooter with customizable loadouts, set in a space station. Developed with the Unity Engine.

202I

ThaumOS

Unmask the conspiracy behind this Windows 95-esque Operating System. Created for LD48, with the Godot Engine.

2020-202I

Rogues & Rumors

A 3-6-player board game about rogues, guilds and intrigue, focused in hiding and uncovering information.

2020

Gravitoids

Asteroids-esque game - control gravity to disrupt and destroy enemies. Developed with the Unity Engine.

2020

Lightstreak

Defense typing game with a neon-like aesthetic and soundtrack inspired by early-Internet era songs. Created with the Godot Engine.

2020

The Long Game

A medieval diplomacy game based on the Prisoner's Dilemma. Developed with the Godot Engine.